BMW sound more aggressive
in sport mode for
a reason It is
not just louder speakers
or fake hype When
you switch to sport
the car changes how
the engine reacts The
throttle gets sharper so
the engine revs faster
The transmission also holds
gears longer which keeps
the RPMs higher and
makes the sound deeper
and more urgent On
many BMWs the exhaust
valves open more too
That lets more engine
noise escape instead of
being quieted down And
in some models the
cabin sound system even
adds a bit of
engine sound inside the
car to make it
feel more intense So
the engine is not
really changing personality BMW
is just removing the
filters and letting the
mechanical drama come through
Sport mode does not
make the car louder
It makes the car
tell the truth