Ever catch your cat
locking onto an empty
corner like it saw
a ghost Most of
the time it's not
spooky Cats have sharper
hearing and better motion
detection than we do
so they may hear
tiny sounds in the
walls vents or floor
They can also notice
dust light flickers or
bugs we completely miss
Sometimes they're just being
cats Staring is part
of how they scan
their space and stay
alert An empty corner
can look interesting to
a cat if it
smells new feels different
or simply has good
watching energy So no
your cat probably isn't
haunted It's just a
tiny predator with giant
senses And sometimes the
corner is empty to
you but not
to the cat