ever coughed up a
tiny white rock from
your throat and wondered
what is that Those
are tonsil stones and
they happen when bits
of food dead cells
mucus and bacteria get
trapped in the little
cracks of your tonsils
Over time that trapped
gunk hardens into a
stone It's more common
if you have deep
tonsil crevices post nasal
drip dry mouth poor
oral hygiene or frequent
tonsillitis They're usually harmless
but they can cause
bad breath throat irritation
and that weird feeling
like something is stuck
back there So if
tonsil stones keep showing
up it's not because
your body is dirty
It's because your tonsils
are acting like tiny caves