BMW engines don't sound
louder in sport mode
by accident they're actually
talking to you In
sport mode BMW sharpens
the throttle so the
engine responds faster and
revs climb more aggressively
The transmission also holds
gears longer which keeps
the engine in a
higher more aggressive part
of the rev range
Then there's the sound
itself Many BMWs use
active exhaust valves and
sport mode opens them
up so more engine
noise gets out On
some models BMW also
adds sound through the
speakers to make the
cabin feel even more
intense So the sound
changes because the car
changes Faster responses higher
revs louder exhaust and
sometimes a little electronic
drama Sport mode doesn't
just wake up the
engine it wakes up
the whole car